(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
TERIMA KASIH!
[Visual: Thank you! - Ayunda Risu]
BERKAT KALIAN, KAMI BISA BERSINAR BERIBU-RIBU TERIMA KASIH
[Visual: Thanks to you, we can shine! A thousand thanks! - Kureiji Ollie]
TERIMA KASIH UDAH BIKIN STAGE INI & HIDUP KAMI LEBIH BERWARNA!
[Visual: Thank you for making this stage & our lives more colorful! - Vestia Zeta]
Terima Kasih!!
[Visual: Thank you!! - Moona Hoshinova]
TERIMA KASIH BANYAK!!!!!!
[Visual: Thank you very much!!!!!! - Anya Melfissa]
Terima Kasih!! Kalian semua keren BGT!!
[Visual: Thank you!! You all are super cool!! - Kaela Kovalskia]
Terima Kasih!!
[Visual: Thank you!! - Airani Iofifteen]
Makasih ya! :)
[Visual: Thank you! :) - Pavolia Reine]
terima kasih
[Visual: Thank you - Kobo Kanaeru]
Ayo mulai!!
[Visual: Let's start!!]
CHROMATIC FUTURE - hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE
[Visual: CHROMATIC FUTURE - hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE]
Welcome to Chromatic Future.
見え透くその心も
Even your transparent heart
この手で make you mine
I'll make you mine with these hands
Wow... Oh baby I need you ずっと
Wow... Oh baby I need you forever
意味をみる度に 上書きされてく欲に
Every time I look for meaning, my desire gets overwritten
重なる eyes eyes eyes 胸を焦がす smile smile smile ねえ
Our eyes meet, eyes eyes eyes, scorching my chest with your smile smile smile, hey
その姿カタチ 全てが拍車かけてく
Your figure, your form, everything spurs it on
恋から愛 愛 愛 毎秒激しくなってく
From like to love, love, love, becoming more intense every second
手を伸ばせばもっと届く距離 危険と知っても試したい
A distance within reach if I stretch my hand, I want to try even if I know it's dangerous
穏やかに恋したい どんなシーンも私に見せて
I want to love peacefully, show me every single scene
このまま stay by my side どこにも行かないで
Just stay by my side like this, don't go anywhere
愛、100％
Love, 100%
止められない感情
This unstoppable feeling...
その手で抱きしめてよ
...hold it with those hands.
もっと近くで 見つめ合いたい
I want to look at each other from even closer
火照る衝動を
This burning urge...
持て余すだけなら
...if you're just struggling to handle it
Hey, what's wrong with me?
何もない普通だし
Nothing, I'm totally normal
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you right now
最初は声を聞く それだけでよかった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough
だけど次第に Y-Y-わがままになった
But gradually, I-I-became selfish
誰かに微笑みかける その仕草に苛立ち 隠せない自分に気づいた
I noticed my frustration at you smiling at someone else, which I couldn't hide
独り占めしたい
I want to keep you all to myself
いっそ鎖に繋いで
I'd rather tie you down with chains
二人きりの部屋 至近距離
In a room with just the two of us, at close range...
行動発言 監視したい
...I want to monitor your actions and words.
思い捨てて眠りたい
I want to throw away my thoughts and sleep...
君の吐息感じさせて
...let me feel your breath.
stay by my side
どこにも行かせない
...I won't let you go anywhere.
愛、100％
Love, 100%
私だけに依存してね
depend only on me...
いいでしょう？
...okay?
歪む愛情の
All of this distorted love...
丸ごと受け止めてよ
...accept all of it.
狂おしい程愛おしい
Maddeningly lovely...
息ができない 行かせないで
...I can't breathe, don't let me go.
火照る衝動を
This burning urge...
後悔聞かせないで
...don't let me hear any regrets...
絶対
...absolutely.
Hey, what's wrong with me?
何もない普通だし
Nothing, I'm totally normal
君の全部知りたい
I want to know everything about you...
I do need you 今すぐ
...I do need you right now.
目を閉じたら
When I close my eyes...
止められない愛が
...unstoppable love...
触れたい
...makes me want to touch you.
私の
Only...
カタチだけ
...my form.
このまま stay by my side
Just stay by my side like this...
二度と離れないで
...never leave me again.
愛、100％
Love, 100%...
純粋な愛だから
...because it's pure love.
止められない感情 その手で抱きしめてよ
Unstoppable emotions, embrace them with your hands.
あぁ 遠くから通い合う ずっともっと近くで 認め合いたい
Ah, connecting from afar, I want us to understand each other even closer.
暴れる初期衝動 持て余すなら LUST
If you can't handle this raging primary instinct... LUST!
Tell me what's wrong with me
何者でもない私だし
Since I'm just a nobody,
君の全部知りたくて
I want to know everything about you.
I do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now!
Oh baby, I need you, I need you ずっと
Oh baby, I need you, I need you, always.
逃げるなら今だよ 勝利を願っちゃって
If you're going to run, do it now, while wishing for victory.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? もし落ち込んじゃうならね
Are you ready? If you're feeling down...
眠気覚ましに 15 minutes
to wake you up, 15 minutes.
耳を澄ませて 拍手喝采 君にほら
Listen closely, look, the applause is for you!
誰もが救世主になれる
Anyone can be a savior.
I will be there in Standby now
今更 正直 飽き飽きなんだよ
Honestly, I'm tired of this by now.
ドラマは残酷 私には日常の味ね
Drama is cruel, but to me, it's just the taste of daily life.
画面ピクセルに挑戦的
Defiant down to the screen pixels,
目に焼き付けなよ 1, 2, 3
burn it into your eyes, 1, 2, 3!
お行儀良くなんて無理 確信からの一撃
It's impossible to behave well, a strike of certainty!
Day by day 衝動的にあらあら
Day by day, impulsively, oh dear!
やったこと全部 意味をなした
Everything we did made sense after all.
笑ってくれたっていいじゃん
You can just laugh, you know,
涙は似合わないから
because tears don't suit you.
VICTORY TO THE WORLD!!
手に入れた勝者の感動は きっと かけがえないはずよ
The excitement of the victor in hand must surely be irreplaceable.
見て てみて てみてよ この今日
Look, take a look, look at this day.
手に入っちゃって
We've got it in our hands!
難解なラビリンス 抜け出せない
An intricate labyrinth we can't escape.
限界ならメーデー 合図送るシグナル
If at the limit, Mayday! Send out a signal.
ドライすぎる世界線のうえ ココはコントロール
On this too-dry world line, here is the control.
拾い上げたワンキル
A picked-up one-kill,
葛藤は私を強くしてく
conflict only makes me stronger.
ハッとするような景色から
From a breathtaking view,
覗き込めるのはシャクで
it's annoying to just peer in.
押し寄せる 1, 2, 3
Rushing in, 1, 2, 3,
死ぬのは嫌あれ トリプル トリップ
I hate dying, oh my, triple trip.
気がついたらラウンド3で
Before I knew it, we're in round 3,
あれれ 隠れていただけ？
huh? Were you just hiding?
泣かないで ファイティングポーズ
Don't cry, take a fighting pose!
叶うなら わがまま全部叶える
If possible, I'll make all your selfish wishes come true.
泣いちゃいそうな毎日に
To the days when you're about to cry,
それが私のゲームポイントになるかも 知れずにね
without knowing that it might become my game point.
VICTORY TO THE WORLD!!
共に掴み戦いたいな 熱く滾った真ん中を
I want to grab and fight together, in the hot, boiling center.
心地いいのこの今日
This day feels so comfortable,
君に染まっちゃって
dying it all in your colors.
Kami floor! Ayo menyala!
God-tier floor! Let's light it up!
Ayo ID, let's go!
Come on, ID, let's go!
Ayo ID, mana suaranya?!
Come on, ID, let me hear your voice!
Baby, もし落ち込んじゃって
Baby, even if you feel down...
Hey, 瞳 ぶれないで
Hey, keep your eyes steady!
Day by day 戻って まだまだ
Day by day, back to it, not yet,
折り返した私にアカウントとって
make an account for me as I turn back.
笑ってくれたっていいじゃん
You can just laugh, you know,
涙はいらないから
because we don't need tears.
ゲームポイントを合わすだけ
Just matching our game points.
VICTORY TO THE WORLD!!
絶対抜くよ あの光で 軌道を
We'll definitely break through the orbit with that light!
忘れられないほどの
With an unforgettable...
勝利を願っちゃって
wish for victory.
境地を行こう GG
Let's reach new heights, GG!
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya (Oh oh)
When the world doesn't go as it should (Oh oh)
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya kau coba lepaskan saja (Iya iya)
Maybe it's finally time for you to just let it go (Yeah yeah)
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
No need to ask why anymore
Jika memang jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed you can't get the answers
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry over it, try to get through the puzzle
Relakanlah karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think
Dah lah saja, oh dah lah saja
Just let it be, oh just let it be
一曲目からもうめっちゃカッコいいよね！その熱さ、感じてるわ！わ！
やばいっすね
Even from the first song, it was so cool! I'm feeling that heat! Wow!
That's crazy!
アドレナリンがわいてくるんだもん
これ走りたくなるっすね
Adrenaline is rushing. This makes me want to run!
おいおいおい どこ行くの？
Hey hey hey, where are you going?
いやいやストップストップ！
No, stop stop stop!
汗かくよ！汗！
You'll sweat! Sweat!
カエラはどう？
How about you, Kaela?
わあ、すごく楽しい
まさか自分がここに立てるとは思わなかったよ
Wow, it's so much fun! I never thought I'd be standing here.
でもちなみにライブはまだまだ長いから
最後まで張り切っていこうね！
But by the way, the concert is still very long, so let's keep our energy up until the end!
張り切ろう！
Let's do our best!
でもさっきからライブの話してるけど
みんなライブのタイトル知ってる？
But we've been talking about the concert, does everyone know the title of it?
今回のライブは題して「Chromatic Future」！
Our concert title this time is "Chromatic Future"!
意味わかる人？手を挙げて！
Anyone who knows what it means? Raise your hands!
こぼが絶対知ってるね
Kobo definitely knows best!
そうですね、一番背が高い人が説明するっす！
That's right, let the tallest person explain!
そう来るかい！まあいいか
Oh, is that how it is? Fine, then!
初めての人も聞いてね
Listen up, guys, for those of you who don't know...
「Chromatic Future」ってのは
カラフルな未来ってことだよ！
"Chromatic Future" means a colorful future!
ホロライブインドネシアは もう5周年になるからね
Since Hololive Indonesia is already celebrating its 5th anniversary...
私たちはみんなデビューから今日まで 一緒に歩んできたわけ！
We've all walked together from day one until today!
それでこれから先も、私たちがカラフルな時間と思い出を創り出せたらいいなってこと
もちろんホロライブインドネシアのファンとも一緒に！
So we hope to continue creating colorful times and memories in the future, of course, together with all the fans of Hololive Indonesia!
そうっすよ、カエラ・コヴァルスキア！メモってね！
そうそうそう
Exactly, Kaela Kovalskia! Take notes! Yes, yes, yes!
さて、皆さんもうわかりましたよね？
さっきカエラが説明したから
Now, you all understand, right? Since Kaela just explained it to you.
ってことでライブも始まってることだし
And so, since the concert has already started...
本日のライブのことをSNSに投稿する際は
When you post about this concert on social media...
ハッシュタグ #holoIDChromaticFuture も
忘れずに付けてくださいわ！
Don't forget to use the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
だってみんなのその…なんていうの、えっと…
情熱が！見たいから！
Because we really want to see your... how do you say... passion!
そうっす！そうっすね！
Exactly! That's right!
打ち間違えないでね！
Don't make typos, don't make typos!
いえーい！絶対投稿してね！
Yay! Be sure to share it with everyone, okay?
でも正直に言って
「インドネシアライブやるんだよ！」って 言われた時びっくりした？
But honestly, when you were told, "We're doing a concert in Indonesia!", were you surprised?
もしもし？聞いてくれる？
Hello? Is anyone listening?
そうっすね！
That's right!
そうっす！あたしも同感！
妹のゼータに共感しているっす そうね、共感ね
Exactly! I agree too! I feel empathy for my younger sister Zeta. Yeah, empathy.
カエラ・コヴァルスキアはどう？
How about you, Kaela Kovalskia?
私もびっくりしたよ
なんかこう「え？マジで？」って感じ
I was surprised too, like "Huh? Seriously? For real?"
なんかこう「え！ついにインドネシアで9人そろって ライブできるんだ！」って！マジかっこいいよね！
Like "Wow, can that really happen? Finally, and with all nine of us in Indonesia!" It's so cool.
かっこいいっす！
It's so cool!
はい、これが初めてホロライブ
インドネシアの9人全員でのライブだから
Yes, because this is the first live concert with all nine members of Hololive Indonesia.
実はこれはホロライブインドネシアのファンに
とても重要な瞬間でもあるんだけど
Actually, this is a very important moment for Hololive Indonesia fans...
世界中のみんなも見てくれるんでしょう？
But everyone around the world is watching too, right?
いや、ちがう？
Or is that not the case?
お答えして
Please answer.
はいはい！みんなありがとう！
Yes yes! Thank you, everyone!
でももちろんこれで終わりってわけじゃないよね？
But of course, our achievements won't just stop here, right?
だから次はこう…世界征服ってのはどう？
我々はレディー！レディー！ レディーレディー！
So, maybe next we can... dominate the world? We are ready! Ready! Ready, ready!
そうっよカエラ！ゼータ！
That's right, Kaela! Zeta!
この機会におけるファンの支援に加えて
In addition to the support of our fans for this opportunity...
このライブを実現させるために支援いただいた
スポンサーの皆様にも感謝申し上げまーす！
We would also like to thank all the sponsors who supported us in making this concert happen!
ありがとうっす！ ありがとう！ありがとうっす！
みんなありがとうね！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
サンキューサンキュー
Thank you, thank you!
ところでこのライブって 何か違うところあるのかな？
カエラ気づいた？ 一番気が利くから
By the way, is there something different about this concert? Kaela, did you notice? Since you're the most observant.
もちろんっす
Of course.
もちろんそうだよ
こぼは気づかないと思うけど
Of course. I don't think Kobo would notice, though.
これだよ
It's this.
私たちの身体いつもとちょっと違うんだよ
Our bodies are a bit different than usual.
かわいい！クルクル！
Cute! Spin, spin!
かわいいかわいい！
Cute, cute!
カメラこっち！こっち向けて！こっちこっち！
始まったなこれ
Camera here! Point it this way! Here, here! It has begun.
ほらほら！こぼのかわいさを見て！
Look, look! See Kobo's cuteness!
これこれ、お尻
Look, look, my butt.
えー！お尻！
Eh, butt!
おいおいおい こぼがカメラ全部乗っ取ってるじゃん
Hey hey hey, Kobo is hogging all the cameras.
こっちにも向けてよ こぼだけには向けないで
Point it over here too, don't just focus on Kobo.
いち、に、さん…はい終わり！こぼの番っす！
こっちにも向けてよ こぼだけには向けないで
One, two, three... okay, it's over! It's Kobo's turn!
ストップストップ！やめてって！
カメラ全部乗っ取らないでよ！
Stop, stop, stop! Don't take over all the cameras!
はいはい… それじゃあ
Okay, okay... Well then...
やばいちょっと息切れた
ライブではしゃがない！ はいー
Gosh, I'm a bit out of breath. Don't fight in front of the concert stage! Okay.
はいはいー はいよ
ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Yes, yes. Zeta is scary when she gets angry.
はいよ ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Okay, because it's scary when Zeta gets angry.
こわいよー
It's scary!
もういいや ゼータがカメラを独り占めしちゃダメっていうのなら... うーん、しょうがない
Fine, if we're not allowed to hog the camera from Zeta... well, it can't be helped.
ファンのみんなと遊ぼう！
Let's play with all the fans!
さっきみんなからも大きな声をもらったわけだし 今度はこぼがみんなに大きな声を出したいっす！
Since everyone cheered loudly for us earlier, this time Kobo wants to make everyone cheer loudly!
はいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes.
そうっすよ、カエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's right, don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's streams.
そう！みんなにじゃなく、みんなとね
Right! Not at them, but with them!
そうそう！そういうことっす！
Yes, yes! That's what I mean!
だってこれから歌わなきゃいけないから まず声を温存しなきゃでしょ？
Since we have to sing after this, we should save our voices first, right?
そうっよ、そんなにカエラの配信時間ほど長くはならないから安心して
That's right, don't worry, it won't be as long as Kaela's streams.
まあいい 大声出していいから好きにして
Oh well, you can scream if you want, do whatever you like.
みんな準備はいいかな？
Is everyone ready?
いい感じ？
Feeling good?
もう出来てるみたいっすね！じゃあこぼから！
Looks like you are! Then Kobo goes first!
一緒に「BOKOBOKOBO！」って叫ぼう！よしいくよ！
Let's scream "BOKOBOKOBO!" together! Alright, here we go!
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBO！
BOKOBOKOBO!
いいわいいわね！次はゼータ！
Great, great! Next is Zeta!
はいはいはい！
Yes, yes, yes!
「ミッションスタート」って言ったら一緒に「スタート！」って言ってわ！
When I say "Mission Start", say "Start!" together with me!
いいか？アアア！ミッション...
Ready? Ah, ah! Mission...
スタート！
Start!
次はカエラ！
Next is Kaela!
よしよし！さてみんな そしてholol3roも
Alright! All of you, and holol3ro too...
「holol3ro！」って言ったら「HU-HA！」で返してね！簡単でしょう？
When I say "holol3ro!", reply with "HU-HA!". Easy, right?
さあさあさあさあ！
Come on, come on!
準備はいい？ holol3ro！
Are you ready? holol3ro!
HU-HA！
HU-HA!
いいわいいわね！
Awesome, awesome!
いいわついに３期生は息ぴったり
Great, the 3rd Gen is finally in perfect sync!
そうわ まだまだ元気がありそうだね
Yeah, looks like everyone still has plenty of energy.
だって、今日の一曲目だけ でももうすごく伝わってくるんだもん
I mean, we can already feel it so much from just the first song of today.
みんなまさか私たちの１曲目が 「100%」だなんて思ってた？
Did you guys actually expect our first song to be "100%"?
思うわけないよな 私もびっくりした
There's no way they expected it. I was surprised myself!
ホシノヴァ気分でライブ開始だなんて！ すごいよね？
Starting the live in Hoshinova mode! Amazing, right?
やばい！
Insane!
かっこいいっすね、しかもさっきゼータとかが歌った... いや違う
That was so cool, especially when Zeta and the others sang... wait, no.
ゼータとか？
Just Zeta?
ゼータとカエラが歌った時は もう本家の「100%」みたいっす
When Zeta and Kaela sang, it was just like the original "100%".
マジかっこよすぎるんだけど なんか、うーうー！ってなってき
It was seriously way too cool, it made me go "oo-oo!".
あんなかっこいい歌を歌ったことあるのかな？
Have you ever sung such a cool song before?
かっこつけてんの？
Are you trying to act cool?
そう、かっこつけてる
Yeah, acting cool.
本物のかっこつけ だってムーナの曲かっこいいもん
True coolness. I mean, Moona's songs are really cool.
だってゼータがいつもスタイリッシュ とかジャズっぽい曲ばっかしょ？
Since Zeta usually only sings stylish or jazzy songs, right?
だからさっき「100%」を歌った時 めっちゃ雰囲気か違う
So when we sang "100%" earlier, the vibe was totally different.
しかもカエラのラップも！
And also Kaela's rap!
なんかこう...
It was like...
とにかくかっこよかった！すごくわ！
Anyway, it was super cool! Amazing!
でも、それだけじゃないよ！
But that's not all!
次の曲が「NEW zomBIE!!」でした！
The next song was "NEW zomBIE!!"!
これだれの曲かわかるよね？
You know whose song this is, right?
もちろんだよ うちの先輩だ
Of course we do, it's our Senpai's!
holoroのパフォーマンスもめちゃかっこよかったよ まるでゲームの中にいるみたいだった
holoro's performance was also super cool, it felt like we were inside a game.
そうっすわ！ しかもバックダンサーもいたし
That's right! And they even had back dancers.
かっこよかったっすね！
It was so cool!
他になんかあったかな？ レーザーも花火も！あと...
What else was there? Lasers, fireworks, and...
すごいギミックがたくさんあったっすわ！
There were so many awesome stage gimmicks!
あのバックダンサーたち あたしのソロライブに雇うっす
I'm going to hire those back dancers for my solo concert.
おっと、もうソロライブの話？
Oh, talking about a solo concert already?
まあ言葉も祈りってやつ
Well, words can be like prayers.
でもこのライブはまだ終わらないよ！ まだまだ！
But this concert isn't over yet! Not yet!
でも...さっき何の歌を歌ったか知ってる？
But... do you know what song we sang earlier?
もちろんだよ 私の新しい曲だから
Of course, because it's my new song.
そうっすね まあいいや
Right. Well, whatever.
まあいい
Whatever.
いやいや！タイトルは「dahlah.」だよ！ 「dahlah.」！
No, no! The title is "dahlah."! "dahlah."!
おおなるほど
Oh, I see!
「dahlah.」だったか... まあわざとだったけど 先に言ってよ！
Ah, it was "dahlah."... Well, I did that on purpose, but you should've said so earlier!
だっていつもそれ言ってるじゃん 本当にまあいいやって思ってた
But you say that all the time, so I really thought you meant "whatever".
それ言って帰ると思ってた
I thought you were just going to say that and go home.
いやいや、かわいそうだから
No, that would be sad.
じゃあ「dahlah」ってどういう意味？
So, what does "dahlah" mean?
人生はしょうがないって意味
It means "life can't be helped".
人生は重いからまあいいやって言えばいいだけ その後人生を続けようって意味
Life is heavy, so you just say "whatever", and it means "let's continue living life anyway".
そうっね、大人になったらね
That's right, once you grow up.
Untung lagunya santai, easy listening, jadi kita sambil keliling-keliling kan ya sapa fans kita, ya?
Thankfully, the song is relaxed and easy listening, so we can walk around and greet our fans, right?
Asyik banget ya tadi ya? Aku juga suka banget tadi dance bagian reff-nya ya.
It was really fun, wasn't it? I also really liked the dance in the chorus.
La-da-la-da-la-da...
Itu... itu beda lagu gak sih?
Isn't... isn't that a different song?
Gak gitu deh. Kayak gitu kah?
I don't think it's like that. Is it like that?
Ya, tapi pokoknya asyik lah ya kalau nyanyi lagu chill, santai-santai kayak gini.
Yeah, but anyway, it's fun to sing a chill, relaxed song like this.
Iya, santai dong.
Yeah, relaxed.
Tapi ngomongin soal santai, kita tuh sebenarnya belum bisa santai dulu. Heh, santai.
But speaking of relaxing, we actually can't relax just yet. Hey, relax.
Katanya gak boleh santai...
You said we can't relax...
Iya, iya, jangan santai-santai! Jangan terlalu santai.
Yeah, yeah, don't relax! Don't be too relaxed.
Karena konser-nya tuh masih panjang!
Because the concert is still long!
Jadi sebelum itu, kalian ada nggak yang mau kalian sampaikan dulu?
So before that, is there anything you'd like to say first?
Mulai dari ini nih, yang gak bisa diam.
Starting with this one, who can't keep still.
Tiga kata saja...
Just three words...
I love you.
Keren, the best. Sangat jelas, ya.
Cool, the best. Very clear, yeah.
Tetap semangat. Tetap semangat menjalani hidup, ya. Dah gitu aja. Pokoknya sampai akhir masih panjang, semangat!
Keep fighting. Keep fighting to live your life. That's all. Anyway, it's still a long way to the end, fight on!
Saranghaeyo! Gomawoyo!
I love you! Thank you!
Oke, kalau aku...
Okay, as for me...
Ya... Semangat selalu! Semangat santai! Hidup jangan terlalu dibawa serius.
Yeah... Always fight! Relaxed spirit! Don't take life too seriously.
Semangat santai ya? Semangat santai.
Relaxed spirit, huh? Relaxed spirit.
Oke, kalau gitu kita lanjutkan!
Okay, in that case, let's continue!
Weits, weits, tunggu dulu. Sebelum selesai-selesai ini nih ya...
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute. Before we finish all of this...
Kita teriak bareng-bareng penonton dulu gak sih?
Why don't we scream together with the audience first?
Iya dong! Ayo! Ayo!
Of course! Let's do it! Let's go!
Oke, oke. Jadi...
Okay, okay. So...
Kita teriak bareng ya? Dalam hitungan ketiga, kita sama-sama teriak 'Chromatic Future'. Oke, ya?
We'll scream together, okay? On the count of three, let's all scream 'Chromatic Future'. Okay?
Oke, oke. 'Chromatic Future' gitu kan ya?
Okay, okay. 'Chromatic Future', right?
Iya, iya, kayak gitu, kayak gitu.
Yeah, yeah, like that, like that.
Oke, langsung ya? Sambil lihat sini, sini, sini, sambil lihat. Ayo!
Okay, let's do it! While looking here, here, here, look here. Come on!
Aku ya, aku, aku. Aku yang penonton ini nih, penonton sini.
Me! Me! I'll look at this audience, the audience here.
Iya, iya, iya. Aku, aku, aku ini deh, yang tengah, yang tengah. Halo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll look at the middle, the middle ones. Hello!
Oke, bareng-bareng ya. Satu, dua, tiga!
Okay, together. One, two, three!
Chromatic Future!
Everything was easy
I did it all alone
so effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic
unfold
got all problems solved
without any setbacks, there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin
dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap,
Like a peacock with wings,
kan kutaklukkan gelap.
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With wind magic, I will invite
semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit melawan dunia.
everyone who is asleep to rise against the world.
We'll never give up
as long as we got the strength in ourselves
we could rise above the pain
we're stronger than that
Walking step by step
trusting my own pace
giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
let it go
It'll never bring me down, believe me
It'll never bring us down, believe me
No matter cruelties, still am I royalty
And when the universe works against me, I'll charge
Let it go, if it's spicy, just sip-sip something, let it go
Let it go, if it's spicy, just sip-sip something, let it go!
Let it go...
I've been living carefree
there's no bitter wars
in the world that can affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold
not letting it show
Things might be bigger than my feelings, so deal with enough
There's no way I can begin
dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever
hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayap,
Like a peacock with wings,
kan kutaklukkan gelap.
I will conquer the darkness.
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak
With wind magic, I will invite
semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit...
everyone who is asleep to rise...
...melawan dunia
...against the world
We'll never give up!
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
We're stronger than them
Walking step by step, trusting our own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
Let's go!
Just believe me, let it go
They'll never bring me down, just believe me
Let it go
They'll never bring us down, just believe me
Won't let their cruelty steal my royalty
And when the universe is against me, I will just...
Let it go!
Come on guys, let's do this!
One, two, three!
Let it go!
hololive indonesia CHROMATIC FUTURE 5th Anniversary LIVE